WILLIAM CONNATSER

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EMAIL: me@williamconnatser.com
PORTFOLIO: williamconnatser.com
GITHUB: github.com/WilliamConnatser
LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/WilliamConnatser

SUMMARY

Hard-working Software Engineer who has been fascinated with technology since the pre-teen years. Channeling that natural interest and curiosity into a profession fuels my daily growth and ambition. Possesses a strong attention to detail, and the ability to work independently with little supervision.

PROJECTS

7/2019

Maze MUD Escape <u>tinyurl.com/yy8o4471</u>
One week group project
React | Python | Django | PostgreSQL

- Multiplayer maze escape game made with HTML5 Canvas and WebSockets
- Largely responsible for the Django back-end and WebSocket implementation github.com/cs19-maze-mud

5/2019

ChallengeJS

ChallengeJS.com

One month group project

React | Express | Postare SQL | Author

- React | Express | PostgreSQL | Auth0 JavaScript coding challenge application
- Worked on all aspects of the stack
- Leveraged web workers to run arbitrary code client-side and run tests github.com/labs13-clone

4/2019

Stockly

GetStockly.com

One week group project
React | Express | PostgreSQL

- Leverages sentiment analysis to predict stock prices and view market data
- Solely responsible for the entire back-end
- Architected data caching to get around API limit restrictions

github.com/lambda-stockly

1/2019

Bitcoin Maximalism <u>BitcoinMaximalism.com</u> Two month solo project

Vue | GraphQL | MongoDB | BTCPay

- Bitcoin-integrated social network
- User up-vote weighting is dependent on the amount of Bitcoin donated github.com/WilliamConnatser/bitcoin-maxi malism

SKILLS

Languages

HTML | CSS | Sass | LESS JavaScript | Node.is | Python

Front-end Frameworks

React | Vue | Blaze

Back-end Frameworks

Express | NextJS | Apollo GraphQL

Django | Flask

Databases

Microsoft SQL | Postgres | SQLite MongoDB

Operations Management

Git | Linux | Docker | Kubernetes | Jenkins Let's Encrypt | PM2 | Nginx | SSH | VPN Netlify | Heroku | ZEIT

Computer Science

Data Structures | Algorithms | OOP

EDUCATION

02/2019 to 12/2019 Lambda School

Full Stack Web Development

- Procured extensive experience programming full-stack web applications, CS fundamentals, and team workflows

EXPERIENCE

1/2020 to Present

Pro Unlimited LLC Jacksonville, FL

Associate Software Developer

- Significantly contributed to enhancements and bug fixes on numerous fullstack Javascript and Node.js tools which made business processes more efficient
- Worked with multiple associates on several projects simultaneously while maintaining solid communication across teams and meeting deadlines

1/2018 to 7/2019 and 6/2008 to 12/2014 WEC Land Services College Station, TX

Software Engineer / Title Examiner

- Architected a web application which organized a large ranch's legal documents by integrating with a FTPaaS API
- Performed meticulous oil & gas title research to determine surface, mineral and royalty ownership of property
- Produced reports based on my research in courthouses using Microsoft Excel and Word

3/2015 to 4/2016

Adecco/Computershare College Station, TX

Customer Service / Quality Assurance

- Garnered experience with nuance surrounding financial and legal services
- Provided quality customer service experiences while utilizing large amounts of empathy and patience
- Promoted from a temp agency to a full time employee with quality assurance duties